Challenging AI to do 100 things
Episode 56
Make the most of it
Let me ask you a question first
Students who use AI for design
How do you use the images you create?
such as this logo, this poster, this illustration
Do you also, like me, just zoom in for high-definition?
and then just send it directly to the boss or the client
Let me tell you
You need to step up your game
You should send the logo like this
This poster needs to be placed in these locations
and then send it
The same goes for this illustration
like this with practical effects
design images with application effects
whether it's directly packaging and sending to the client
or create a presentation PPT for the proposal
you'll find it useful
And this is no simple mock-up.
Look at how well this logo fits on the product surface.
the back of this bag
the back of this bottle
There is also a backpack partially obscured by hands and accessories.
Everything is perfectly presented.
Some students might ask,
I can also do it with Photoshop
Indeed, but you will still encounter some issues.
Not to mention whether everyone can do it with PS
Can the product's surface decal be done this well
The key point is it's troublesome.
After you send this set over
the client asks you to make more changes
Aren't you screwed?
Not to mention the previous visuals being done in vain
This set of decals was also done in vain
You have to redo everything all over again or many times over
This is truly top-tier torment.
Now with the help of AI
Everything has become incredibly simple.
Just use this, the photo editing software everyone is very familiar with
Open the AI mapping function on the Home page
First, upload a product image or an environment image
Then upload your design here
If it's a logo
You can also remove the background with one click
After uploading all the images, at this point,
AI will automatically recognize the product for you
or the 3D information of the environment
can also help your design
It can naturally fit from any angle.
Then you can freely adjust your decal
on the surface of the product
freely drag the position
adjust the size or angle
Look how smoothly I can drag it around
Your design will also tightly adhere to the product's surface.
You don't need to think about it yourself
perspective or surface logic
Once the position is set
Just click save directly
This simple and highly efficient mapping method
Isn't this much more convenient than using Photoshop?
No matter how many times the client asks you to redo the work in the future
you can easily handle it. Alright, that's all for this video.
If you also like my videos
Remember to like, follow and favorite
I'm Bob
See you in the next episode